It was so much. We had seven days to figure that piece out. I had seven days to also conceptualize
how I was going to spend these 20 minutes with the vice president of the United States already
knowing there are going to be certain limitations, trying to figure out what my audience might expect
and what I know I can't deliver and deciding what I want to deliver. What was something you wanted?
What was something that you would have wanted to say that you knew could not? I think I would
have wanted to just have conversations about what black people care about and allow them to hear
from the vice president what she cares about. But the reality is, is that there's only a certain,
like the vocabulary of the vice president that can come outside of the office is very limited.
And I don't mean that in any terms of like shade. It's just the reality. There's so much. And that's
why when people tell me to run for office, I feel like they're so misinformed on what it takes to run
for office. I'm sure you get that as well. But there are so many layers to politics
that prevent people from being completely present all the time.